Guide to the Louis Gottschalk Papers [ca. 1927]-1975
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: General Correspondence
  - Jun-Aug 1961 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Sep-Dec 1961 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Jan-Mar 1962 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Apr-Jun 1962 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Jul-Sep 1962 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Oct-Dec 1962 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Jan-Feb 1963 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Mar 1963 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Apr 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - May 1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Jun 1963 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Jul-Aug 1963 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Sep-Oct 1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Nov 1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dec 1963 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Jan-Feb 1964 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Mar-May 1964 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Jun-Aug 1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Sep-Oct 1964 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Nov-Dec 1964 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Jan-Feb 1965 (includes 2 undated letters) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Mar-Apr. 1965 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - May-Jun 1965 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Jul-Sep 1965 (no August dates) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Oct 1965 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Nov 1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Dec 1965 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Jan-Feb 1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Mar-Jun 1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Jul-Sep 1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Oct-Dec 1966 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Jan-Feb 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Mar-Jun 1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Jul-Sep 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Oct-Nov 1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Dec 1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Jan-Feb 1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mar-Apr 1968 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - May-Aug 1968 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Sep-Dec 1968 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Jan-Mar 1969 (includes an undated note) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Apr-May 1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Jun-Jul 1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Aug-Dec 1969 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Jan-Mar 1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Apr-May 1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Jun-Sep 1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Oct-Dec 1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Jan-Jun 1971 (includes some undated letters) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Jul-Dec 1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Jan-Apr 1972 (includes some undated letters) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - May-Dec 1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Jan-Mar 1973 (includes some undated letters) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Apr-Aug 1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Sep-Dec 1973 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Jan-Feb 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Mar-May 1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Jun-Sep 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Oct-Dec 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Jan-Feb 1974 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Mar-May 1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Series II: Topical Files-University of Chicago
  - Departmental Correspondence, minutes and notes. 1944-1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Departmental Correspondence, minutes and notes. 1965-1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - History Committee December 1933-March 1934 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Crane Memorandum 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Curriculum Committee 1942 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - College History Course 1949 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Report on the State of the Department of History as of January, 1973, Text (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Report on the State of the Department of History as of January, 1973, Text. Appendices (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Report of the Committee to Evaluate the Dept. of History, 1 March, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Gottschalk Fellowship Committee (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Hutchinson Fellowship Committee (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - List of U. of C. History Ph.D.'s (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - New Courses in History (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - U. of C. Extension Division; Home Study Syllabus; European, History 1789-1914 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - History 1; Readings in Historiography (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - History 1; Readings, Part 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - History 1; Readings, Part 1. Part 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - History 1; Readings, Part 1. Part 3 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - History 1; Readings, Part 1. Part 4 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Scammon Case, 1941-1942 (U. of C. Radio Round Table) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Senate Memorial, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Conference on Military Policy, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence with University officials (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Lectures given in 1937 by professors of the Social Sciences on the nature of their specialties; Part 1 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Lectures given in 1937 by professors of the Social Sciences on the nature of their specialties; Part 1. Part 2 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Lectures given in 1937 by professors of the Social Sciences on the nature of their specialties; Part 1. Part 3 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - C.E. Merriam on Physics and Politics, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems Organization of a Chicago Group (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems. U of C Group, March-May 1943 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems. U of C Group, June-Dec. 1943 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems. Correspondence with Central Committee, March-Dec. 1943 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems. Correspondence with Central Committee, March-Dec. 1944 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems. Circulars from Central Committee. News Letters (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems. Circulars from Central Committee. Summaries of Replies from Cooperating Groups, Problems 1-4, 8-10 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems. Circulars from Central Committee. Summaries of Replies from Cooperating Groups, Problems 11-20 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems. Circulars from Central Committee. Analyses of Problems 3-9 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems. Circulars from Central Committee. Analyses of Problems 10-19 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems. International Conciliation publications. Fortune (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Universities Committee on Post-War International Problems. Circulars, Correspondence from NWU (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Series III: Topical Files-General
  - Biographical Data' Louis Gottschalk (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Gottschalk's early essays (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Master's thesis; "The Development of the Republic Idea in Jean, Paul Marat" (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Gottschalk typescript on Marat book, ca. 1927 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "The Gottschalk Case", Louisville, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Assistants (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Instructions for assistants (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Costs of research, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Costs of research, 1929-1930. 1931 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Costs of research, 1929-1930. 1931.1932-1935 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Typescript of R.R. Palmer's dissertation; "The French Idea of, American Independence on the Eve of the French Revolution," 1934, Part I (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Typescript of R.R. Palmer's dissertation; "The French Idea of, American Independence on the Eve of the French Revolution," 1934, Part I. Part II (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Social History, 1932-1938 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Army Air Force Committee of Historians, 1943-1946 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - University of Washington appointment negotiations, 1947-1948. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Responses to Understanding History (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 1954-1955 trip to France; Guggenheim and Fulbright awards (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Carl Becker symposium, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences, 1957-1958, Biographical data on fellows (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Strategic Air Command, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Festschrift for Gottschalk, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - American Revolutionary Bicentennial Commission (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence with authors (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Reviews by Gottschalk (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Random notes on the nature of history (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Bibliographies arranged by subject (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Personal finances (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence with Donald Lach (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Social Science Research Council Funds, 1935-1937 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Social Science Research Council Funds, 1935-1937. 1938-1947 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Social Science Research Council Funds, 1935-1937. 1941-1945 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Social Science Research Council Funds, 1935-1937. 1957-1963 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Social Science Research Council Funds, 1935-1937. 1946-1974 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Social Science Research Council Funds, 1935-1937. 1964-1970 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Social Science Research Council Funds, 1971-1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Requisitions (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Requisitions (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Requisitions (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Social Sciences Research Council; Committee on Historiography, 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Social Sciences Research Council; Committee on Historiography, 1942-1943, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Social Sciences Research Council; Committee on Historiography, 1942-1943, 1945-1948 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - "Use of the Personal Document"; Social Science Research Council Bulletin 53, 1940-1945 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Social Science Research Council; Agenda, Board of Directors' Meeting, Sept. 11-14, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Social Science Research Council; Agenda, Board of Directors' Meeting, Sept. 10-13, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Social Science Research Council miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Social Science Research Council miscellaneous, 1956. 1957 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Agenda, Board of Directors' Meeting, Sept. 9-12, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1951-1952, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1951-1952, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1951-1952, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1951-1952, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1957. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1957, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1957, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1957, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1957, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1957, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1957, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1957, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1957, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1957, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1957, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Scientific and Cultural History of Mankind; Correspondence, 1957, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - SCHM; Press Notices and Releases (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - General Assembly and Executive Board of UNESCO (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - U.S. National Commission (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Paris Meeting, 1952. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Meeting of Seventh International Congress of History of Science, August, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Paris Meeting, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Working Papers and Instructions (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Contract and relevant correspondence (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Volume IV Associates and Collaborators, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Volume IV Associates and Collaborators, 1954. 1955 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Volume IV Associates and Collaborators, 1954. 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Tentative Outline and Plan for Vol. IV (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Tentative Drafts of Introduction, Vol. IV (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Maps, Illustrations, etc (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - The Journal of World History; Memoranda and Notes (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - The Journal of World History; Memoranda and Notes. Authorities Suggested (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Journal Correspondence with authors, undated-May 1952 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - June-Dec. 1952 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - 1953-1956 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - SCHM; News bulletins, information papers, etc., 1952 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - SCHM; News bulletins, information papers, etc., 1952. 1953 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - SCHM; News bulletins, information papers, etc., 1952. 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - SCHM; News bulletins, information papers, etc., 1952. 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - SCHM; News bulletins, information papers, etc., 1952. 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - SCHM; News bulletins, information papers, etc., 1962-1967 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - American Historical Association, 1956 & previous (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - American Historical Association, 1956 & previous. 1957-1959 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - American Committee for the Study of War Documents, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Session on French Revolution, December 30, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - The American Society for Eighteenth Century Studies, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - The American Society for Eighteenth Century Studies, 1969. 1970 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - The American Society for Eighteenth Century Studies, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - The American Society for Eighteenth Century Studies, 1971. 1972 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - The American Society for Eighteenth Century Studies, 1971. 1973 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - The American Society for Eighteenth Century Studies, 1971. 1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - The American Society for Eighteenth Century Studies, 1971. 1975 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Lectures Abroad (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Public Lectures, no date (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Public Lectures, no date 1928-1937 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Public Lectures, no date 1932 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Public Lectures, no date 1937 Social Sciences Lectures-Gottschalk's (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - The American Society for Eighteenth Century Studies, 1971. 1937 Social Sciences Lectures (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - The American Society for Eighteenth Century Studies, 1971. 1939-1946 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Council on Foreign Relations Lectures, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Council on Foreign Relations Lectures, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Public Lectures, 1947-1957 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Public Lectures, 1947-1957, 1958-1969 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Public Lectures, 1947-1957, 1971-1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Bibliography of Gottschalk writings (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Reprints, no date-1936 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Reprints, no date-1936. 1938-1939 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Reprints, no date-1936. 1940 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Reprints, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Reprints, 1941. 1942 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Reprints, 1941. 1943 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Reprints, 1941. 1944 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Reprints, 1941. 1945 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Reprints, 1941. 1946 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - "Theory and Practice in Historical Study; A Report of the Committee on Historiography," 1946 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Reprints, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Reprints, 1947. 1948 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - "Goals for Jewish Living," Symposium, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Reprints, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Reprints, 1949. 1950-1951 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Reprints, 1949. 1952-1954 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Reprints, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Reprints, 1956. 1957 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Reprints, 1956. 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Reprints, 1961-63 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Reprints, 1961-63. 1964-67 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Reprints, 1961-63. 1968-72 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Reprints, 1961-63. 1973-74 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous reprints of Gottschalk book reviews, brief articles, etc. (Filed in separate BOX shelved next to BOX 24) (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence; University of Chicago Press, 1935-43 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence; University of Chicago Press, 1935-43. 1947-67 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence; University of Chicago Press, 1935-43. 1968-74 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence; Knopf, 1936-49 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence; Knopf, 1936-49. 1950-69 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Scribner's, 1971-May 1972 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Scribner's, 1971-May 1972. June 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence in re Letters of Lafayette to Washington, 1969-74 (second edition) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence in re Letters of Lafayette to Washington, 1969-74 (second edition). 1934-48 (first edition) (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Drafts of Letters of Lafayette to Washington (LOLTW) (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Drafts of Letters of Lafayette to Washington (LOLTW) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - LOLTW, photostats and transcriptions (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - LOLTW, photostats and transcriptions (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Scot, Foresman % Co (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous publishers and editors, 1931-34 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous publishers and editors, 1931-34. 1935-58 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous publishers and editors, 1931-34. 1960-74 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Board of Jewish Education, 1940-April 1942 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Board of Jewish Education, 1940-April 1942. May-Sept. 1942 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Board of Jewish Education, 1940-April 1942. Oct.-Dec. 1942 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Board of Jewish Education, 1940-April 1942. Undated (1943?) (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Board of Jewish Education, 1940-April 1942. April-Dec. 1943 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Board of Jewish Education, 1940-April 1942. 1944 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Board of Jewish Education, 1940-April 1942. Undated-April 1945 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Board of Jewish Education, 1940-April 1942. May-Dec. 1945 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Board of Jewish Education, 1940-April 1942. 1946 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - College of Jewish Studies, undated-1944 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - College of Jewish Studies, undated-1944. 1945-47 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Report on a conference on the Jewish Experience in America, May 1948 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1964-Feb. 1965 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1964-Feb. 1965. March-April 1965 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1964-Feb. 1965. May-Sept. 1965 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1964-Feb. 1965. Oct. 1955 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1964-Feb. 1965. Nov-Dec. 1965 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1964-Feb. 1965. Dec. 1966-Jan. 1967 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1964-Feb. 1965. Feb.-March 1967 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1964-Feb. 1965. June-July 1967 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1964-Feb. 1965. Aug.-Oct. 1967 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - B'nai B'rith, Nov.-Dec. 1967 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - B'nai B'rith, Nov.-Dec. 1967. April-Aug. 1968 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - B'nai B'rith, Nov.-Dec. 1967. Sept. 1968 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1968 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1968. Nov.-Dec. 1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1968. Jan.-March 1969 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1968. April-Sept. 1969 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1968. Jan.-May 1970 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1968. June-Sept. 1970 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1968. March-May 1971 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1968. June-Dec. 1971 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1968. 1972 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - B'nai B'rith, Oct. 1968. 1973 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Annual Meeting of B'nai B'rith Hillel Commission; Washington, D.C., Nov. 22-23, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1963-1967 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - B'nai B'rith Annual Meeting, Washington, D.C., March 4-6, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of Board of Governors; N.Y., March 16-19, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Surveys, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Minutes B'nai B'rith Administrative Committee, Washington, D.C., Aug. 26-27, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Resolution and budgets, Oct. 1967 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Budget, Oct., 1967 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Agenda Book, Washington, D.C., Oct. 28-30, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Budget, Washington, D.C., Oct. 28-30, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, Washington, D.C., Dec. 2-4, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Budget, Washington, D.C, Dec. 2-4, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Annual Meeting, Washington, D.C., Jan. 6-8, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, Washington, D.C., May 11-13, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Budget, Nov. 2-4, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Budget, Nov. 2-4, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting, Washington, D.C., Mar. 8-11, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Budget, October 1969 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Annual Meeting, Washington, D.C., Nov. 29-Dec. 1, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Budget, Dec., 1971 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Weil Institute Executive Committee 1970-1974; Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Student Papers
  - Student Files, Ac-As, Acomb, Frances Adams, F. G. W. Anderle, Josef Asch, Walter B. Ashton, John (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Student Files, Ba-Bu, Bailey, Charles R. Behen, David M. Behen, Dorothy Forbis Berwick, Keith B. Binyon, Millard Pierce Buck, Stratton Berks, Richard (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Student Files, Ca-Car, Cappadocia, Ezio Carey, Raymond G. Carlson, Leland H. Carson, George Barr Jr. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Student Files, Cat-Co, Cate, J. L. Cates, Jane Lohrer Cayley, Charles Everett Centner, Charles W. Jr. Chada Cook, Lester Couse, G. S. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Student Files Dan-Dav, Daniel, Marjorie Davis, Florence Davis, John H. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Student Files, Den-Dun, Denney, Emilie Sumi Destler, Chester McA. Doyle, Bertram W. Drzewieniecki, Walter M. Dunn, F. R. Dunnington (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Student Files, Ea-Fu, Easterby, J. H. Esterquest, Frank L. Fagg Fajn, Max Funk, Arthur L. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Student Files, Go-Gr, Godfrey, Eleanor Smith Godfrey, James L. Gould, Stanton W. Grathwol, Robert Green, Philip Jackson Gross, Hanns (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Student Files, Ha-Hau, Haas, Arthur G. Hall, Thomas R. Halperin, Samuel William Harcave, Sidney Samuel Harr, John Lauren Haugh, C. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Student Files, He-Hu, Herr, Richard Hirsch, Helmut Hirschfield, John M. Hoffmann, John Wesley Hotchkiss Howe, L. L. Hudson, Harris Gary (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Student Files, I-Jo, Iggers, Georg G. Jackson, Luther Porter Jefferson, Alfred Carter Jensen, Christian A. E. Johnson, Gustav Elwood Johnson, Thomas Walter (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Student Files, Ka-Ko, Kaminsky, Howard Kelly, Alfred H. Kennedy, Melvin King, Arnold Kimsey Kovacs, A. F. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Student Files, La-Lev, Lach, Donald F. Ladenson, Alex Leaman Lee, Ulysses G. Levett, Ella Pettie (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Student Files, Lew-Ly, Lewalski, Kenneth F. Lingard, C. Cecil Lucki Lyon, E. Wilson (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Student Files, Mac-Mo, MacDonald, Janet McGee, Gale William McNeil, Gordon H. Maehl, William Harvey Mohler, Samuel L. (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Neil, William M., Newman, Edgar Students' Papers (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Pacheco, J. F., Padover, Saul K. Palmer Palmer, E. Schuyler Parker, Harold T. Peck, George T. Penner (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Student Files, Ph-Pu, Philip, W. B. Philips, R. Craig Popper, Annie Marie Puzzo, Dante Anthony (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Student Files, Re-Ro, Read, James Morgan Riches, Naomi Ricks, Joel Edward Rockwood, Raymond C. Ross, James Bruce (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Student Files, Sa-St, Sanger, Donald Bridgman Sarkisyanz, Emanuel Savage, William R. Schoenrich, Carlos O. Scoville Slovin, Norval L. Smith, Charlotte Watkins Sparks, David S. Strevey, Tracy Elmer (Box 32, Folder 5)